Hi guys, welcome back to our channel for
today's video, I'm very excited.
Our video is a reminder for a day.
That means everything we will eat will be
karenderia food.  Of course, we have
special people with us.  We actually went on a ride
eating karindirya food and it was
really delicious so I'm excited
now.  Breakfast, lunch, dinner and
snacks.  All snacks.  You are hungry.
Oh wow.  Sorry, sir.  My sister is at work.
He didn't get to say goodbye.
Just smile, sis.  Just watch.  We will eat
for you.  We'll just take it out
because we're just going to eat it.   He
said don't take him out anymore.
So when we were kids, we would eat porridge down there
.  Porridge with egg.
I'm taking out from the green store because my mom bought it for me
.  The house is on the left.
Oh, not porridge.  What
you're eating there is topsilog.   There's no
porridge either.  In a large
pot.  What is the most delicious
fast food you have ever eaten?  I like
mix-and-match and then the lady
mix-and-match bro.
Spaghetti.
I don't like spaghetti.
Okay.  Sorry.  My porridge is
always mine.  Mom is counting on me, I know.
I don't think
you can go there.
Yes, why?  It's just next to
our house.  Because he's taping.
You need to rest.  Beauty rest,
he will buy me porridge.  Okay.  Let's eat
.
Let's go.  I'll drive fast.   Okay,
let's go.
Hello.
Because it's late.
I thought you came to say hi then.
He said, "You know what? You know what?
We're going to the curenda.
Just watch us."  Ma'am said,
"Just until you smell like that."  Oh,
just admit it.  Ouch.  Still working.
That's okay.  I want to quit.  I want to
quit just to eat.  Are you tired?
Yes.  We'll take you out so you don't get
tired.  It's like you're either here or
we're complete.  You are beautiful.  You look like a
lion.  Put the camera down.  How beautiful
[laughter] oh.  That's a wolf cut.  Maybe
you didn't know you became a lion.
Wow!  It seems like they are attracted.
Bye.  Oh, usually when saying goodbye,
you need to give it days and days ahead.
I just told them last night that I wanted to
do a carindirya.  We used to want to
do it, but my brother was in Europe.
You can't do anything because you don't have a
driver.
Hey, thank you.  We have been waiting for you.
Thank you.
Welcome.  I think my outfit
[music] for today is cute.
I should have gone to bed earlier.  You are terrible
.
I'm like a girl girl because I watched
all my vlogs, everyone was wearing pants.  And
today's a special day because it's
Carinderia day.  So okay see, you're
laughing so hard,
those animals there
[laughter]
you're also noisy with the lion, who are the other
two, Ed and Eddie, Eddy, the one who seems
stupid [laughter], isn't there one Eddie
and one Eddie, is
n't the other a woman, who is Ed, who is it
among the three of us, I'm the only one,
ma'am, bro is making us go around, ca
n't you just be a [ __ ]? Just look at the
trouble, look at it.  Answer
Ed.  Ed.  [laughter]
That's okay, bro.  Even if you post and get
furious about it.
Your face [music] is fast and furious there.
Don't be in a hurry about it.
You are together.  I'm just hungry Edang Ed
.  Okay, that's all that really registered
with me.  Let it go.  I accept it.   This is
really the father.
That's only 60.
60 but you are here in the small one that looks beautiful
.
You are here on the small road.  You can't do
that.   The
road is big.
You have a big face there.
[laughter] Is it just big?
Personally
[music]
let's eat
or the woman has her own green light,
the driver just eats there.
Just eat there, man.  This is what I
really want to try.  Morning sun eaten.
This is delicious.  So this is Micheline Recognize.
It makes me proud.  Filipinos are really great
.  We will try him.
Mom, what do you want?  I like barbecue.
I barbecue.  When we were kids,
we used to eat barbeque on the
corner, it was delicious for Php8, right?  I don't
know how much now.  Wait a minute,
I have an explosive announcement.  Oh
[whistles]
to our compatriots abroad,
don't ever forget about
Top because Top has great rates, zero
transfer fees to banks and mobile
wallets and very fast delivery.
Within 5 minutes, you will receive your
shipment immediately.  Even when we're abroad,
I use tops because it's economical,
fast, and reliable.  Because that's money.
We really need to be careful with money.
They have more than 15 million downloads.
This country is really special
because I grew up here, I played here
when I was a child, and my father lived here
.  Top is available in Bahrain.  For
our compatriots in Bahrain,
the tops are now available there.
You can use it to save money and
really experience the topen.
We have so many questions from people
we know there.  Why can't we
download the top cent?
The top cent is only available in selected countries
.  So if you see
your country listed there, download it.  Use it right
away because it's really beautiful.
If you are here in the Philippines, you don't
need Tapsan because it is not yet
available for downloads here.  But
you can accept your shipment.
You can do this in your bank or mobile wallet, or
you can pick up your money at
cash pickup ranches.  You can use my
promo code top I ban to get
awesome bonuses.  If
you send $50, you will immediately receive $70
.  Of course, I still have a
gift for you.  This is from
me.  This is exclusive only for
our OFWs.  So download Taptop
Send and use my code top Ibana because
that's where we'll be choosing who will get an
iPhone 17. So if you're from the US
including Hawaii, UK, UAE, Bahrain,
Canada, Australia and select European
countries, the
winner will be random.
Wherever you are, I'll send this to you.
[squeaks] Ah, beautiful.   Let
's get back to eating.  That's fine if
you want to try the eggplant salad.
Okay.  That's enlightened.  I think there was something wrong.   I had
grilled chicken liver at the
barbecue.  We asked for three
sticks and then the one that was stuck was also stuck.
Besides, it's me.  Vegetables.  How delicious.
Jackfruit milk.  Okay, everyone, sir.  Let's try
.
Can I take a picture?
Yes.
How much more rice?  Sorry.  He said, "Can I
take a picture of some rice?"  Why are you
shaking?
Oh, Micheline God.  God bless you and
you're done with us.  Ma'am,
you are so talented.  How did you
get Michelin?  Suddenly,
our customers and I were congratulating
them.
Thank you too, ma'am, for
giving me this opportunity.
Oh, you are already well-known because
I really looked for the best restaurants.
We need to support
our locals.  Ma'am, I'm excited.
Thank you.  God bless you, mom.  Thank you
.  Congratulations again.  Awesome.
Two side dishes.  What do you want
to eat?  Come on.  Hello.  What are
you requesting?  Rice, please.  Rice
and a side dish.  Are there two of you?  Yes.  Okay, mom, let's go
.
Wow.  Go ahead and take it.
Increase your food intake.
Hey, I'll add more.  Let's
eat.  I'm excited.  Let's go.   Have
you ordered yet?   Place
your order there and then charge
me, sister.
Yes.  Who wants to eat?  You too can eat
.  I have a pocket.  Char.
No, no.
Ma'am said she was fine.
Okay.  Let's share and share.  Just one bite
.  This is a
bite
.  Liver.  That's mine.  Oh, delicious.
Eggplant salad.  I really can't
eat without chili.  What?  Let's eat
.  This is the chili.  Where is it?
I didn't touch that.  Mm.  They don't do
that.
We'll be able to smell it there.  It's expensive because it's expensive.
That's okay.  You will be full.  Thank you,
Iban.  Love you ma'am Ibana.  Thank you for
pushing me to choke.
Okay, let's eat.  Or I'll barbecue first.
That's it.
Hey, that's okay.  That's okay with me.
I love you, I love you.  Mm.
T's bought us bananas.
Thank you.  Thank you.
Let's try.  Cheers.
Cheers.
Delicious.  Delicious.
Love you, ma'am.  Thank you.  How
lucky are you, ma'am?  I promise I'm your
wow sweetie.  Do you see that?   You
have to try the bar.
You'll take it out later.  Thank you.
Oh, ma'am liked it.
They said take out.  They really want
us to eat
[music]
the fat is solid the
bibka is delicious
hey
mama because she said it was delicious I just tried it
mama the bibingka at the end
ma'am's bibingka is gone that's
my appetizer
wow it's really good barbecue it's really solid
lempo
what's that I can do this it's
really delicious I'm just a toy the barbecue is
delicious then chili
paan
what's the best so far bro
the barbecue.
Wow, our barbecue favorite,
escalope salad, is delicious.  Don't you have anything
like this?  This is how it looks.
This is
the ugly part of you.  Liver is swollen
.  Where are your wells?
That's eaten.  It's hard to take a step forward.
You want jackfruit?  The jackfruit is ripe.
We'll try that next.  Grilled tuna.
Cheers.  I want to dip it in more
deliciousness.  You know from the amount of food
in front of me.  I already know.
We love their pickled vegetables.
These are the vlogs I want to
devour.
Same.
Mm.  Is jackfruit delicious?  These two are
my favorites.  Barbecue is also rare.   It's
so bad that just breakfast is already sacred.
These two don't care.  What?
Do you have any objection to that?  They are
speaking.  I hope you remember
we're still here.  It's delicious too.  Tuna.
Tuna.  Is he okay?  Hey, ma'am,
that's high in sugar, ma'am.  Ma'am, you sound like a
tasteless child.  Hey, that's just sauce ice
.  It's not sweet.
I'm just your skin, mom.  I'll try to find some medicine.
So far, this is my favorite
barbecue.  Then I like the way they look and
I also like their sparkle.  It's
also delicious just by eating it.
But everything is really delicious.  Hey, try
my sauce.  That's delicious.  Soy sauce.
Seriously.  Four what?  Takeout.
What else are you taking out?  Okay,
we can go boating now.
How delicious.  Promise
day I'll give you cheese.
Oh wow.  For me,
baby.  Eat, son.
Add lots of cheese
.  Anyone else want to eat?  Eat, okay?
Just order or.  Is it?
So there's no food left.
We left the others out.  There is still salt
inside the cella.
Is my food fatty?  This is it
then.  Oh, my dear,
maybe I'm fat.  What are you avoiding?
Ghost.  He broke my cellphone.  So,
please.  Just apologize before complaining.
It was fixed.
Let's try this with
alcohol.  Where is the boat?  'Is there a
problem?'  Oh yes, you've never
been interested in anything before.  Just give him water because
his sugar level is rising.  That's why we
banned him.
Mom is stubborn.  Mom said she was stubborn.   It's
really tough.  I feel like when
our parents get older,
they become like babies.
We've been
rocking this baby baby for a long time, just a little bit,
diabetic-free people, don't you want to
continue with diabetes? No wasted
food, we'll take it out and
we'll still eat it later. I'll bring my
brother's banana.
How much did you pay for it? There's a
lot of it, not just this food, but
also the other tables. What's that
ketchup?
What am I going to do here?
Why only 150 ping rice?
Ma'am, thank you, ma'am, he's the one who
gave me the banana [laughter],
I brought it. I mean, dear. I'm crying
[cheers], I'm
really an idol. Ma'am, promise.
What are you doing? Ma'am, we're doing well. Ma'am,
thank you, ma'am,
thank you, ma'am, thank you,
ma'am, thank you, ma'am, I think this is it.
Oh, he's giving away
biscuits. Oh, and even a cat. Oh, he even bought
water. Oh, he didn't have a drink. He's
cute. Oh, he's cute. Give it to
the guy who gave the
banana to the guy who was buying bottles. We passed by.  I was surprised when
he suddenly handed food to
a homeless person and the cats.  He
himself peels eggs, so
let's give him 10,000 more because
he shares his blessings.  Come on, brother
.  Oh
oh, why are you here?
What blessing did you give me?
Oh, I'll give it to you too, I gave
you a banana yesterday, right?
Yes, what kind of water did
you give him?
I'm also eating you, I was suddenly humiliated,
I'm really bitter.
That's my friend Daniel, you gave me a
blessing, I also gave him a blessing,
you angel, you're amazing.  Or
I will increase your grace.
Oh, 10,000 shine-share
your blessings.
Oh,
we have light.
Why don't you have a light?
Nothing.
Hello everyone, ma'am.  Yes, that's all for you.
I was surprised because we were on our way home and when I
saw you, I was so relieved even though it was raining.
Oh, suddenly, ma'am is feeding me.
Ma'am, this is really mine, ma'am,
I'm shaking.  Why?  Now I have
money because I'm
selling bottles, I
wish I was riding a tricycle.
Shivering.
You're so kind, you even feed the cat.
I saw him peeling it himself and
he didn't know we were there because
we were on our way home.  Do you know
I'm here?
He didn't say anything when he saw it.  Why are you here,
sir?  Keep it up, okay?
Ma'am, thank you ma'am.  Promise me,
I'll be happy.  I'll give you a
box and your light.  What is
your name?  Giovan Baleva Perez Jr.   Are
you from here?  Go ahead,
ma'am.  Thank you, ma'am.  [squeaking]
Brother, give me money.  I'll eat
you, my
dear brother, ma'am.  Promise.  Wow [squeaks]
my brother is so cute.  You know he's a bad
boy, but he has a soft heart.  He doesn't have
slippers.  Even when
he is in need, he still helps.
So people like that are funny.  Yes.
Plus, he's funny.  My brother is a little
confused.  But he has a mammoth heart.
Thanks, brother.  Keep it up.
He doesn't really do that for the camera.   He
said
yes, he was surprised when he saw it, and
even yesterday he said he was giving
food to the person sitting there every day.
Yes.  Yesterday it was bananas, today it's rice
with eggs and a dish because they say it has blessings
.
That's touching.  Filipinos are really different
.  I didn't expect to see something like
this today.
I just had a brainstorm.  Is that where it was broken?
No more.  That's it, it's broken.
[music]
Thank you.   That's
enough.  It's okay with you,
brother.  Thank you.  Mom chose but
only three.  You know it's not his
favorite.
Don't worry, boy.  Oh boy, the taste of the
stoned meat is delicious.  He's still hot [music].
Oh come on boy.  There is a child.  Don't worry,
boy.  Right.  Why do they treat their
boyfriends like that?
That comes from your blood.
That's your son
.   Did
you taste the end?  Come on, boy.
Eaten.  Ah, that's what happened to Niog.
Mmm.
Mom, your kidney is the only one that has been implanted with
something.  I hate salty things.  Yes,
mom, that's not a toothbrush anymore.  It seems like
I wiped it.  I brushed my teeth
yesterday.  Oh.  Yes.  What more do you want, boy?
I don't want that to have saliva [laughter]
boy.  Wait here, boy.  Okay, okay.  One more thing.
Another girl.  Ah airplane jogjog
your airplane is scary.  [laughter]
Maybe
that's just a bill.  Is that a joke?
He's not a diner because
you can sit down at a diner, but he's a
diner [laughter]
he's there, we were outside the
diner, we bought his yambang.  Mm,
I'm moving.  It's delicious, I
want to go sour, do
you want a boy, boy,
boy, boy,
boy, [music] either way, you're
a boy [laughter] a boy, it's delicious, this is my favorite, that's why
he always takes me home when he's passing by,
I'm my favorite,
I love that,
suddenly the rain poured down heavily,
so [music] tomorrow I'm going back to my brother
Daniel who lives in Kali to give him a
little help and what
he needs.  I sent my other
staff home first because they got wet from the rain so
they could take a shower and we spent some
time before having lunch at the next
restaurant.  [music]
The hacienda is ready.  Wow.  Thanks,
bro.  So here we are now in
our mother's bastion.  It's a good thing the sun suddenly
came out because it had been raining earlier.  It looks like it will
rain again later.  We grew up here.
We also buy here, but the
packaging there is gone.  Nothing was finished and
I bought 25. I remembered
I was crossing the street to buy
tapsilog.  I don't know where
you buy tapsilog,
you won't get it there.
Nothing.
There really is.  What did I just eat?   There is
no dream.
He must have just dreamed it, so
you asked the old man about it.  Topsilog
before.  Come on, you're going to crash.  He
really thought this was his stronghold.  Crossing the
anoid.
Iron Man.
His headache is really bad.   I'm
just asking.  There used to be a shelter here
.  Here.
Where?
Here.  Before?
This or.  It used to be
real.  Mm.
Huh?
Yes.  [whistles]
I told you what 10,000 is.  I have 10,000.  What do
you think of my stupidity?  I never
forget my childhood because it's
all important.  What?   They say
there is.  It's still green.  I don't know what
you think.  Or you are another one.  No.
I said 'yes' and in the end I said it seems like there is
.  I'm sorry.
Sorry,
you are right.  I was wrong.
It only happens once a year.
When he makes a mistake,
he accepts it.  Come and show me how
you walk.  This is cool here.  Keep going.
[squeaks]
Yes.
Walk to GTA.  How?  How?   It's
even hotter.  It's not that hot.   It
feels like being pregnant.  Look carefully.
It's like I'm pregnant.  You are beautiful
to me,
lips ma'am, you are wearing a diaper, it's raining,
we need to hold
on, I can see what you said, we eat what
we ate when we were
kids, that's the house we're
walking to, this is the computer shop
we play at or he's picking you up, there's nothing left,
what's the name of the company
I'll tell you if you make a mistake.
Should I go there?
Yes.  You always have open hours there.  Uncle
there.  There it is.  They didn't remember.
I'm the only one who remembers.  Oh, this is it.
That's delicious.  Porridge.  We eat here.  Here's
Mona's porridge.
You can eat takeout now.  I'm here.
I also buy tofu here.  What are
you buying here?  Do you know what happened here before?  Oh
yes.  There is no end to this.  Opposite that, there's a
tap.  There is chicken and noodles.
You're done.
That porridge was my favorite
when I was a kid.  I could eat that
every day.  Do you remember me when
we were kids?  Oh my god.  Jomar, include that.
What question do you have for me?  For lunch.  Oh
yes.  Do you know breakfast, lunch?   This was
our dinner then.  Sorry Jomar.
Sorry.  What is this porridge?  What about you?
Breakfast.  Breakfast.
Breakfast snack.  Wow.  Luga for snacks,
rolls.  ' Did you milk the bilo-bilo
tikabaanong?  Yes.  Lunch for lunch.
That's what I want, and it's a real pig.   Do
you like your finished product?  It's okay,
I want to see their top.  You're
addicted to Topsilog, but you're a loser at the
computer shop.  It's actually a computer shop.   I
promise you'll feel like
you're still offline, even if
you don't know the name of the computer.
Or go straight up the stairs.
Yes, the stairs are steep and sometimes a
mouse will run over your feet while you're
playing.  So I remember that.   That
seems about right [laughter].
Mom remembered.
That's why he picks me up sometimes.
You're an addict.  He's right.  He's always like that
.  But you said, "Will a
computer shop make you rich?"  Oh, he's rich.
He always fought with us when we were kids.
Why?  Can a computer shop really make you rich
?
Yes.  We practiced there and now
we're vloggers.  You need a fast
brain and fast hands.  Who will be happy?  I
raise my feet.  Five porridges.  The plain one
with egg.
40 used to be 20.  Do you have lumpyang tog too?
I want that, let's go ahead and take a
peek. Okay,
you want porridge.
How much is the whole thing? Let's buy it. Let's give it to you.
Lumyang tog is my favorite.
And tofu. How much is it, ma'am? This is just this. The
pot is not complete. The pot is not included. Just the
contents. Yes, how much is it?
We bought it all. How much is the
whole thing?
Php,000.
Okay, let's take it. You have a profit there.
Oh, that's not what we
have. How much is this? All
600.36. Just list it, sister. Go ahead and include this.
Sister. Let's give it all away. No, so we can have fun. We don't have anything to eat. This is not a cafeteria. What is this? Buying everything in the corinderia challenge. Give it to the troops. Pips,
tofu. That's all.
Everything. Even the bean sprouts. Egg whites. Everything
here. Then you're asleep. So this
cafeteria is open for 24 hours tomorrow. Do
you really want to eat here?
Yes, at least now we'll all escape
. We'll be together.  Come on, let's eat
.  I'm hungry.  When the barbecue melts immediately
.  Let's go.
We'll eat our lunch first.  You know you're
most excited to eat.
What is that that you can take your eyes off of?
You said, "
Okay, what are you doing?"
It seems like he's already shopping.
That's equal.  I'm checking to see what's more
.  That's it.  Let's eat
.
Thank you.
[music]
I'm really kidding, but it brings
me back to when we were kids and
mom didn't want to cook because we didn't have a
budget for food.  This is
our race.  Space.
It's also convenient because it's also lime.
We didn't ask for
pork because we just had a baby.  This is delicious
.  Oh, you're hungry.  Or J is jealous of
us. You're taking back
your question to us for lunch.  Lord, bless
this food, may it be a stream of
powerful blessings for each of us.
Thank you very much Lord for every day in
Jesus name.  Amen.  Amen.  Cheers.
Delicious.  This is it.  Delicious.  The
sauce they have here is really delicious.  Yes.  This is
our dish.  The tofu.  Not only those who
love tofu with pork.  This is the only thing
I want, the tofu.
Wow.  Their chyo oil is just delicious.
You ate the same thing before.
No.  They don't have any.  Why do
n't you have this?  Nothing.
Let's try.
Delicious.
I love this.  Maybe that's why he's special to
me because this is exactly what the child tastes like
.  You, bro, are still so
delicious
that I often buy it for him when he's
sick.
I'm often sick, so I
always take time out or get tired during taping.  Because it was
your time to tape.
This story is true.  You know, sometimes
we buy our food here.
Camille Pratista's mom will teach that
.  That's famous.
Oh yes.
Despite that.
Yes, because we're proud to be from here, like wow
.  That will play out outside of what
the tick is.  Now what can you say about
them saying that's where mom lives
and they're laughing, we look so proud,
man.  If you're proud,
your cravings are just that delicious
.  How delicious.
You know what feels like comfort food when
you remember your memories of being a baby.
Oh, put it here, you're welcome, oh,
let's try the tapak tap tapsog,
you didn't like the tapsilog
here, it's just porridge, I get takeout
here, the tapat is also delicious, the loser
closed down, yes, they do it that way because it's delicious, you
know, they just relocated,
you know, their branch just grew,
but this one looks
really similar to that one, it's
nostalgic, what do you call it,
nostalgic, it's
like this, childhood memories.
Mom because she is still always cleaning the
table.  When we eat, do you
always turn us upside down?
Takeout for all of us, please.  Besides, many
guys say I don't
see my mom's side of the family.
Our grandmother.  How old is mom?
88.
Our grandmother.  But I never really
showed it.  I did that on purpose
because mom loves walking in the
park.  Yes.  That's his favorite.  I don't want to.
People say, "Hey, I saw you on a
vlog or whatever."  Then
his routine will disappear.  Especially since my
mother has Alzheimer's.  She will be worried for
her safety too.
We still love our grandmother very much.  We just don't
mention it in every video for
his privacy.  He is the one who
supports mom with everything from medicine,
food, housing, everything.  You can't let
your mother leave you.
He leaned over.  But mom loves to
share blessings, so she
ran to Santa.
You win.  What can you do to help
this barangay?  Since you're not sitting, you can
still help.  You don't need to.
You're the only chairman in the house.   Let
's take a position.  He is the chairman.
What are you?  Vice-president.  Did
I become president when I became president?  President.
President.  Treasurer.  No one will suffer,
really.
No one will steal from this, not
even a peso, it has never been stolen.  Yes,
maybe you stole?
No.  Nothing.  Admit it, we didn't,
we just stole maybe Php10, mom.
You know, it's true that Mama is so stingy
with us, but she's so generous with others, so why is this
okay,
chairman? Many of you are already
shocked that we haven't tasted anything yet.
We don't have any money there, because
you've already tasted everything I
was born with here. I haven't tasted anything.
Bananas are cute, and melon juice is
not a thing.
Mola works, but ma'am, you're
still taking our money,
that's all, chairman.   It's
not so they can learn to strategize because
if you provide everything, they won't
learn to strategize.  They will never
learn the fight of life.   That's it
.  Or
maybe you learned.
You're making me taste the hardships of life.
I learned to take my money.
I learned.  It really depends on each
parent how you discipline
your child.  Maybe when I have children,
I won't give them everything.  Char
also immediately believed what he said.
Your way of disciplining
us, mom, is a bit harsh, it
seems extreme
because
that's what's needed,
that's what mom did to you too, if I were you,
what kind of discipline would mom give you,
softer? How are you always alive?
How will they fight the winds of life? Is
n't that a softer version? Isn't that what you
have,
while you've been strong and
all, of course there's still time that we
wish you were softer, so that's what we
want for our kids.
I love you.
Kiss me, mom.  Kisses, mom.  There is nothing
like that.  I'm sure
you know that when I call
mom now, I always say "I love you."
He'll let me down.  I'll call
him again.  I said I love you.  Love
you too.  Bye.  Love you.  Love you, mom.
Love you.  Love you.  Why should
we teach her to be soft, mom?   It's
not me, okay?  But
he's softer now.  I love you.  Wow.  Wow.   It's
really hard to grow up.  Mom, there are so
many big streets with mail.
Where?  You bro, what would you change
if you had children?  Aside from the fact that you won't
take your son's money, right?  Will
you do that?  It's not like
your experiences, of course you'd think
I didn't like it that much at the time.  So if
you don't like it, I won't do it to anyone
else.  It's like you take the good ones
and then you don't make the ones you don't like
.  That's all I'll teach you.
You know this, right?  We were surprised when it
came to his grandson, Gabriel,
our nephew, and sister Amira's son.
He is very soft-spoken.  It's like
he can't scream.  Any grandmother would ask that
question, you grandmothers.   It's
terrible, but we've never experienced it with a
child, it really has to be a bit tough.  When
we are late, I really can't accept that
Gabe is also studying English.  We
have a hanger.  If you make a mistake, just flip it over,
mom, you have a hanger.  There are so many
broken hangers.  Don't clean up anymore.
That's okay.  He even complained
that the hanger was broken.  If
you make a mistake in class, does mom beat you
or scare you about what will happen
to you?
So I'm like Lord, I'm praying for everything I
can, I'm praying for
my child, I see that the two of them are studying,
I said yes, Gab will taste the
harsh discipline, he said Gabriel, I
will pick you.  When I actually saw it,
I said, "Huh, that used to be our mom's dinosaur
. I wish
her face would disappear
or something like that."  Why is that?  To the grandson?
Everyone is different.  Ask
the grandmothers.
I always hear that.  Actually,
the grandmother was very kind to her grandson
because I love to spoil my
nephews and babies.  Brother
will give it to us.  Next
kiss
Alexis [whispering]
let's call.
Okay.
Yes.  Or that
we'll find out if I have a new permit and
I'll spoil it.  I will provide everything the
speaker needs.  Speaker,
grandma is in a hurry.  Grandma is dying.
Can I have a video?  Just calm down.  No
child is calm yet.  They just have a question for you.
Hello, sister.
Hi, sister.  How are you?
Okay, sister.  Mom asked, "You're the one to
ask." I was embarrassed.
I don't want to be embarrassed.  When are you going to do it?  Oh,
what can I do, get married first?  That's right, sis,
I love that.  Thank you, sister.  Thank you
.  Bye.  I love you.  Why would
you make it even prettier if it's the same
destination?  But you can ask like when
[music] do you plan on having kids?
Yes.  When are you going to make that?
Will do.  When do you plan to have children?
Yes.
When will you do it?
Bro, it's okay when you're ready.
I'm just using all the tools.
What are you?  Take care
of all your belongings.  What
will you do?   What a
great idea
.
No, not every day, every night, oh, what's wrong with you,
you're welcome.
Yes, I'll tell
you, I'm a milkman, just take care of
me.
Not gone.  What did you say first?
Milk.  Oh, that's a lifetime.
My mother really thinks that her grandson is
okay when he's a senior.  While we used to have
no milk, now later on, when we are
seniors, ma'am will leave
money so that when
her grandson is senior, he will have milk, okay,
lifetime, even if the child is drinking fresh milk,
yes, even if it's powder, when you are
senior, you will always have total milk,
don't delete that video,
you know, I don't have
porridge anymore, I agree with
you, next week they will make
what is that or mine is scratched, huh?  You can do it, right?
Very good.  Mom,
your egg is poor.  It's a beautiful place to live, it's
just yellow.  Jom joms for not
knowing how to eat porridge.
Mom even served it.  Oh, but
mom didn't serve us.  But when he's
really different, he's like that with everyone else.  Tell me it's
not delicious.  Oh, delicious.  [squeaks] What?
Rice for lunch.  Include this.  Include
that.  Include that.  Tofu.
Now you're together in porridge.  Or so it goes.   Is
that really delicious or is it something Jomar has already passed on?
Our total is Php7,200
for all of that, all the porridge,
all the puto, all the eggs,
85 eggs. So we have about 100 orders,
15,000, let's dole it out,
thank you.
Yes.  Thank you.  Thank you.   Take a
break.  We'll go there first.
Thank you.
Your porridge here is really delicious.
That's your mom's recipe.  We used to live in
Skinita, but then
we moved here.  My grandmother died and went to
my aunt's house, then to my father's.  So it's just a
passing thing.  So the
best recipe is from grandma.  Yes.  It was just a mess
before we had anything
finished.  But he's been like this for 10 years
.  Was it Bao City before?  Let's go.   Let's
give it up.  It's hard to act
when my dress is wrong.  Sorry.
I want to get dressed.  It's just wrong
now.
[music]
Eat inside.  Come on, let's go
.
[music]
We have a lot to eat.   Sit down
.
Hey [music]
[music]
The [music] place was really chaotic
so we left.  Suddenly,
we stopped riding.
I should still be giving away money.  Then I was shocked to see that there were
police there.  I'm not a police officer or we didn't
call or we didn't call
unless it was really required
[music]
because
we're just going to eat.  We were surprised when
the police suddenly stopped.  My brother even joked
earlier that he was going to catch you, ma'am,
but he just helped me keep watch.
Yes, they are kind.
So later we'll just give them
[music] as their snack.
Children are jumping.  Or we used to be like that
when we were kids, I was walking down this
street.  [whispering] Hello.
[cheers]
[laughter]
The
purchased porridge is still being given away.  They are the ones who give
.  I'm not there anymore because I want to be
calmer.  But we're very grateful
to you and your support.  Thank you
guys.  You are awesome.  I think the
police are stressed.  I'm sorry sir but I don't like it
when someone gets pushed [music]
or gets stuck, or when someone   Let's
see if we can give away some
money.  No.  I'll just give it to
you.  Just comment.  Let's
go.
Sister, come on.  The one with a child.
Thank you, mom.  Child.  Bye.  [squeaks] Let's go have
dinner.
Our freshness is gone.  It's tiring.
I'm tired of them.  This is long hair.  This is a
gangster first.  So we'll eat here at
Vivian and Bulalo's tops.   I
want tops,
I want bulalo.  So let's go have
dinner.
Wow, that's delicious.
Wow, crablet.  The quantity.
They have a lot of food.  It's a
mango.  The moa he used to say was
fat.  It's true that I actually gained
weight before because of
my diabetes medication.  But
my sister is very supportive.  He doesn't
see before I gain.
He said you didn't gain weight.  Besides, I
don't want him to say, "Hey, you're fat."
We always need to support each
other.  Even if one person gains weight, they're happy, it's up to
you what you want.
As long as it's still healthy.  Mm.  As long as
he's okay and out of the hospital.  This is
mama semxy too.  What is your secret?  I just
try to eat healthier and move.
Hindi will be together.  I don't like to
restrict myself, but as
much as possible I choose healthier
options.  Honestly, the thing that has helped me the most
with my diabetes and my weight is
walking 10,000 steps a day.  That's it.  It's
hard.
Let's go for a walk, guys.  Going home.  Hey ma'am,
we've ordered eight taposilogs.  How
big is a serving of bulalo?
Two orders, please.  Sister, increase
my bone marrow.  Sister, look at the one
in front.  You can take a look.  Someone
just saw a lot.  Your saliva.
That's great.  Besides, he himself is the owner.
Ma'am, look at this.  Maybe
you'll be inspired.  Maybe you want to cook for us again like
our mother.  And my brother is the one who
will help.  Where can
I do that for you?
Come in now.
I can do that.  His diamonds are beautiful.
Does Ashe have one like that?  I'll buy
the ash.  How much?  Please support your
brother's business.  What is it?
The diamond standard.  Follow if
you want that kind of standard.
Did research.  I'm sourcing.  Those
natural and love diamonds, jewelry,
stones.  We'll have lunch soon.
Your child will come later.
We are going to have lunch.  We're going to have lunch.  Lunch again.
Lunch.  The prices are
really amazing when you see them.
This is their IG and they have a FB.  So
there you have it, your gift check.
She is beautiful.  When you get married there.  Oh,
you guys are looking for a wife,
the diamond standard.  This is the
joke.
There you go.  That's the crazy day.  That's
the marrow.
Wow, [ __ ], is that serious?  I just want
to see a
little bit.  That's not allowed.  Why?
Who wants it?  You wasted 10,000 hashes
on eating the whole thing.  That's the first one.  Yes.  Come out
later.  When did I scam you?   We have
someone with us.  My assistant
also pays for us to
eat.  So I don't have anything free.  I also don't
accept anything for free because of course, it's the
person's effort, the food.  Oh, I
really don't like x deals.  That's a deal
.  I just want to promote.  10,000
ong of chili.  Help me.
You guys really helped.  I'll put it aside
because I'm eating.  Ugly with money.
Mom, you're not even 1k yet.  Guys, help me
guys.  I have PH,000 gash,
guys.  You agree, right?  10,000 to him is
only Ph,000 to you.  Or maybe
you need 10,000.
You are so rich.  He has money and
he also has diamonds.   The
next time I cook,
I'll use diamonds.
That's it.
Delicious.
Oh
wow, that's so spicy.  Good luck,
everyone.  Wow, the bite is inside, as in,
biting.  Let him bite.
It's just an insect, it's just a bite.  It's not a
bite.  You can't do that.  I'm going to
bite you.  Of course,
there's nothing really spicy yet, you might not be able
to handle it.
Nothing yet.  He hasn't even chewed yet.
He is here.
That's just on the side.
Woo!  Sour!  Mom, let's do a challenge.
I am called [laughter] by you.
Oh, that's easy.
Oh no spicy challenge.  It's up to you
.  Mom, don't do it.
I'm not even halfway there.  There is no
such thing.  What are you guys saying?
The soup is delicious.
Or let's try chicharon flower.   This is
my favorite thing to drink.
How delicious.
Mom, it's liver again.  That's a favorite.  Yes, indeed
.  Are you tired?  Let's try the
bone marrow.  [music]
Mmm.   Did
n't you split it first so it would be one
big time?
Wow, I love the soup.  Don't do it.
The challenge is right.  That's it.
Yes, ma'am, that's enough.  That's right, ma'am.  Maybe
that's bad for
wow, how delicious the maro is.  I'm going through something
myself.  Oh my god.  Do
you remember when we were kids, Jollibee Mukbang?  Yes,
these are our first videos.
Favorite, huh?
You are not included.
Next message, that's your sticker for trying
kinilaw or bulalo.  Cheers,
everyone is doing great.  It's my first time here
at Vivian's place.
Oh, that's terrible.  Crispy feet.  You thought you were still catching up
.  Let's try the crablets.
Mm.  My favorite thing about crispy
skin is this one.  There you go, crispy feet.
I am a shrimp.
You know everything we ate was delicious,
from morning, afternoon, evening, snacks,
we were done eating.  Very delicious.   Very full
.  And as a
carindirya because it really started as
a small stall.  I told
Ma'am Vibian a story earlier, but
the huts were banned, so
she became like this.  It's like an enclosed carinderia
restaurant.  Looks full.  Very
shaky.  Oh.  Hey, we're the same.  Wow.
Absent.   Let's
not get
too carried away, we're really full.  What a delicious
meal.  I enjoyed this video,
which is all about snack food.  The food is very delicious
.  Also, the
Michelin-starred restaurants.  And it
really grew.  It makes me proud.  Karenia
feels more homemade and closer to home.
I gave you your 10,000.  Yes.  This is
nothing.  Just give me PH00 in return.   That's
terrible.  You said you didn't help anyone.
That's the end, please tease
your chili, it's okay.  We can afford to
ask for alms, so if
you see that she's a bit strict with her mother,
she really needs it because
our mother is really stubborn.  Didn't
listen to the doctor.  Thank you for the
delicious meal today.  I'm in,
thank you.  I enjoyed it.  I also enjoyed
that you missed these foods.
Because when we were kids, we were the ones who
actually ate tapas for lunch and dinner.  Because
our mom is
busy with Mona's taping.
K